you're gonna get another it's already
okay and then we were supposed to go
through so you know okay and the idea is
that if you become an ACI teacher in
just useless time don't you - yes to
specialize the most difficult choice
which is not a law school you can choose
the kitchen really understand the
business exists around me okay so she
just escaped you kind of have a choice
you got the basic you're gonna get a
basic puzzle that you can teach that ACI
course one French it Nabila cool you can
see you can
okay okay
if you're the kind of commercial my
greatest commentary to Jessica Marie
cooks from the ranch across the
and it has a full set of items time you
stolen on board eat them off almost
occlusion you could have a caramel a
sealer master's degree and what's most
Buddhism I guess that's what a typical
every kilometer and then you could do a
specialty in coastal areas of
commercials in tears from Sutra to
almost a like a comparison with my
keister sketched a pin put in its bottom
I kiss the sky course font my garden I
started it know the natural world
remember your name but is this and
October
okay we'll take five yes the things I
met Pettingill get leads to purchase a
charm commentary tsongkhapa's most
famous book some mysterious technique in
the garden
it's incredible good okay so you don't
have to do any of those master's degrees
when you're building a nice porch at the
monkeys did my most improved to Fuji
book along with that large by
specialized Miss Lucas's boots l0d
master to almost double is my students
it touched my sedative master it's kind
of meditation master master de la
mochila master or in the garden invested
them are still come over Sarah okay
disappoint I just was supposed to stall
because they broke some equipment really
good in Austin yeah the world my mother
yeah hello hi let's get going the right
separate our judge
okay we're gonna do lahrman new material
we've done I'm a demon over material
let's see you can look up
baam space pa ba M space PA and we'll
hit the right place
bum BA bum ba ba m space PA it's unique
it won't it'll occur once in this text I
predict be a.m. space PA
you never thought before me neither
yeah that's it good
okay here we go he's talking about the
first of the six primary negative
emotions which was uncovered
oh she's cheating what - now that you
had the whole outline of the ACI
training - just open your mind
that's cm now you can appreciate all its
bit of a much - that's how much
uniqueness different levels double Chelm
that doesn't what about it
it has many different about no Cheney as
many different teachings you know the
significance lower school mistress :
way of thinking about the study of the
desire line you okay
yeppity-do chief are you polka fighting
over not seen neon exhibition live in a
cave are you to be shared and that's
okay - yes - yes directed by material
things know who gets yes leave us and
rocks at associates stove but Hatice it
all came here today it's on a higher
level we should learn to share a team I
don't know she comes in sharing if I ate
the more relying it's okay to like
chocolate chip option but it's not mine
the party it's Virginia no yes Thorne
yeah but immersed in that Scientology
supuesto past your motion you see Annie
yeah there's smart desire and their
stupid desire yes Melanie his underlying
shares his cookies at the national
Genesis in Virginia but I won't repeat
change and it's not a bad thing applies
exactly at the Masonic anything but
multiple it's it's all good in your
whole life is a tissue paper so I
believe when you polish it just live in
your desire okay
July yeah I'm on your side makes the
world huh but that most of the delicate
it's just a bit all right now if we take
desire to be attachment to yes there's a
like you know school did certainly News
News News Corp meditations it's
cumbersome it's carissima dopa come back
on or you can say kangaroo anymore skies
catch that kangaroo in Australia with
the kangaroo Canada thing in them gamba
means this stupa means beautiful Grozny
yeah I agree meditation Stratton
immediate at say meditation I mean
that's enough a famous example of it is
King routing engine is nominated
premiere at what what is this I'm not
gonna he doesn't teach it here onion
bûche that mistake yeah yeah he doesn't
teach it here but you know it's an old
abhidharma
I just thought I'd miss that I bet that
a man you meditate what do you call you
get
what's that disease where you lose your
legs and valleys in Kagame gangrene a
little tiny spot of green here mining
cos it on that touch because it starts
to spread your skin is rotten it starts
to spread and you can see the bone of
your skull I said the poisonous of our
store movie this voice on your
meditation Chatham's you do your whole
skull regenerates always it's a such a
tip when you wash it and then you move
it down to your body its massive and
tell you Donatella but the question you
do the meditation scene and it gets all
then all the threads break but don't so
slim.i it's a Russian sailor so who's
gonna bite what can you write the
building was it not Daniel
but I must abide in you which is the
earth we made our own break we throw
alia that is come Nika to the devil
assignments could pitch a Donna's
nobuta just a quitter Freeman not as
long as in charge but pakka Brigitta
there won't be anything any wizard
Nietzsche was the cat's old house she
made a house out of Adobe
it's like nuclear dota summer visit us
at the car door my sisters Dania when
you're sure about it but don't worry
because it's in - yeah Manila might see
the Sun one day mm will be empty yeah
Bridget supposed probably there's no
water enough water for two son you know
it that's it
the way a key on California California
New York then you dry up the ocean
it was gone she lessen your desire
that's called skeleton meditation item
is it that's a he has another one get it
done all right so we're gonna go through
this one here we go sauce Dean Young
born
yumbo means how can you fix your desire
coq au vin what you tell people or your
body oh man yeah which means dupa has
matured how distasteful or growth
norepinephrine offense new year means
practice PST PST practice de l'armée du
what is me Dupin mean me number one okay
what smartball read the quran and it
means you peel the skin no doesn't
attach to the stop looking at yes leave
um yeah I used a laser with Roscoe
frigate at CVCC your quarrel it is
magnetic so no sound Jalen a paternal
coxed eight we're all state disgusting
authority to let me do that since the
next time you see this woman or man
who's married already to somebody else
catch the rascal that was Yuka come come
with quality it might not work
my name is called might work
Maura but it might not work I don't yet
a better meditation to do these hires
Bush call person and say look suppose
you do steal this man or okay that
poster
now karma is Manish commentator will
always lose your partner for the rest of
your life karma and I don't want the
petty - to work on someone's wife yes
hmm I discover the quarrel sometimes
this will work okay not in a bed door
motor suppose it's caca spitting
sometimes it's called number - new
question state and it's a Christmas take
a second one number per watt number
thought about soonerlater this person
will die and there are more get
disconnected from the rest
question in England the charcoal
Mariotti Veruca are in quarter that's
violet sativa chill connect change to
your arms and legs is the quartz because
I stopped lead us with turkey not my job
to show ya it's just it's an officially
oh this person's good at the book
because I stuff serious growth in the
private nurse it's like disgusting to
think don't hop quartering the cadaver
but just a Murdoch rip them into
producer about and then you hang the
part of you but don't be rash it's
already chest discipline and other
people cogs mug that said really J but
we're all gonna be quartered this woman
you're trying to steal from her husband
yes the mudra it's gonna get courted
also it's a salmon appraised at me at
the pasta massa
alright so that will help you not have
desire a touch too much time for my
teammates Gilani
it'll Kiribati networks always seminar
about the treatment this works sometimes
Buddhists are about it in like that next
caller number palm back we don't have
that word word doesn't know that word I
but I looked it up he's now at the
source material not a really nice
visualize visualize irritant my I don't
know my dad used to say my artistic of
ideal if you fall in love he I'm like
eighteen years old girl check out her
mother first
I'm glad you've listened to your mom and
then raise it anyway okay so number
pombe means your skin will rot it
doesn't touch the vibe dude cause I mean
yes there was a line you think about
their fingers about to choose you know
don't you come through conga - she here
- a really means conceive of them in a
certain way bones okay I think about my
mom yes ye my me look at that I think is
bones like a question of care okay barks
here's the question it would look like
anybody else's bones questions elites
you know have an affair with yet the
Ranger do we the question if they need
that go six well unless it's Halloween
okay certainly Cohen I don't know okay
alright okay
mmm by the way there's a more formal
teaching
okay I knew you'd say yes yes Mel I went
and got it for you it's from the
scriptures in the gotcha course which
means the Gish
yeah they have a nicely put
no annuities nine steps each egg or
adultery meditation cut them more okay
he just mentioned a few of them on the
nine parts delivered en disgusting
meditation Dagobah system
that's for lettin temperature is Devi
tend to daughter first Oh Cosmo yeah so
it was Casa with the top fishing net in
nature okay
in fact what the z-table warned Pierre
about if you are attracted to this
person's yes live as pavilack I know
body Taylor look at her for my specific
patient is rotting okay that's it but
don't make a cut of it for my to
the girl with it if you have a breast
yes yeah bicep do a Muslim see they're
biting but it's too good to be me
there's a breast rotting okay got it
cool happy okay number two if you have a
suggestion answer sex I'm sorry married
Patricia not
yeah imagine maggots growing I've
beautiful which I wanted drill into
Kotori
suppose I do that couldn't hurt it is a
positive okay like you watching
something like this then think about
okay did you got it you're not the only
one who wants to drill into this person
it's okay yes my egg and it's a small
white warm moist mess I need two kinds
of worm I mean one you did the earth and
you find before they get to eat you
don't fly it doesn't see that no okay
and they will eat you if you die today
but just yes and do you already see that
square table you will be there meet you
could be there dinner today okay number
three number three if you are attracted
to this person
yes smell fairly fried Zabu for Cle at
the maturity echo said i'm one like if
you get near them and you're like they
say menstrual blood has the mystery
man's nearby they're like animals
they're like there's some subconscious
yes about the patron that's in there to
this mountain chain you could you have
this problem stuff to the smell of the
rotten water and pus that comes out of
their body it's tough to Zappa when you
read a bishop in CLA tornado thing yes
the which they approach often mentioned
the smell of a human body worth smell in
the world
I haven't smelled it yes it's a beauty
no not poor
like the worst smell in the world at the
I had it which is Apple a meeting a
number of State George Soros the richest
men in the world at new him some about
the media with his daughter and she was
gonna support yeah it's one of our
congregation died so I was a monk in the
temple but no it was nice because I'm
here's this lady who can support yeah
Austin is yes but almost realization
about the potential by say no I can't
tell the admin Yahoo yeah he's a good
friend
on digit now and when I walked in and
they keep the room very cold cuz they
don't want the feel cold anything and
then there's they take your blood out
and if they put they were pumping his
blood out and you know how they keep you
for three four days they can come see
you through the read now they can walk
quickly before it gets hard so I sat
there for two three hours and did his
part Oprah yeah eligible okay so if
you're attracted to a person's body
Frank yes live respite Budokai that I
might deal a alive II agree but a
few minutes after she must think about
how they're good if the person you're
attracted in such a good rule
nice of Mogu Cassini great Syracuse
lantern when you peel the skin on the
glove is the mighty that's when you do
the red one crassness stick in the
ancient tank a strange texture here it
showed a divine creation divide mr.
Kawashima treated but question yes
that's supposed to be alright number
five remember that if you're attracted
to you guys not get cut very pale very
beautiful Mexican lady a beautiful
golden color
I know color
that's good skin so it's worth question
then do the green thing
don't oh it's as Illinois wish okay what
do you call it mold please
it's the body when it rots it turns
green quieter than your things you sure
what the lasing gonna start recall it
anyway you understand I'm sure about
Pineda more it moves the skin and it
should be eight we call in tibetan we
call if you get green green means your
skin turns green and it starts to follow
change it to green
yes the bomb driver to say the question
for me it's like it's okay I got started
by them something like that all right so
I gave on a chopping of their number
City sushi if you're attracted to the
diet muscles wish to occupy means
shall get buzz no chat girth it means
that big muscles but you must how do you
say that
bill yeah good you know in in India tell
Sonya watch still if you're fat it's
beautiful okay Wendy is so sure Papa
notoriously with don't see the church
the bus anyone who was big active just
America's up with a woman there's no
that over food them and it will change
10 you know so anyway in those days but
I was so taken by treating the Pedowitz
at time bugs and mice and I don't care
if we should that I can the cubit okay
that's number six
no chase are you disgusted that's who we
are and that way it takes cannot
imagination to be attracted to someone
to not notice they are dead meat nor the
protection of our budget was to open my
lady fani prosti Meza sexual attraction
to someone because you know you just
look at them and you're like oh green
moderates in a converted on which only
that's why people drink wine I think
they can I can forget who's really there
Luke get wanna chop it by the way I mean
a higher school excessive Oh shush : you
can be attractive forever the Motor City
verdict I did not say that and say
means fantasies super sexy body he was
with the Super Hornet a lovesick da and
that's fine
yet that's wonderful maybe it's because
we feel the possibility of that we are
attracted to people now more than
vitamin A Sonia because the main shape
you will da Mosta you will still have
the same husband Waterman's we're of
Cuba Nagi you still have a head he go
back so higher school please Josh :
you should be planning to make an
immortal body but there's no y el mas
una GQ GQ Sturm I know that's jumping
okay look gay palaca pinion Umberto
Russia if you're a track yes the way the
person moves West public eye you know
and the guy is like a machine of a taco
sauce you know if the get get get me
inside yes gather as no change then you
do the number to propose new visitor
keep your arms are gonna get divorced
from your feet from your shoulders you
know again if some others day let's go
to my men they're gonna divorce the body
that is veloute still number eight
so listen supper rubella chopping
Americana Boucher there are parts of the
body which are bone just chill and the
most famous attractive one is the teeth
okay somebody has such beautiful white
teeth so oh and you ought to keep the
class nobility and so teeth or other you
know zoo but that noise
you know yeah momento ricochet let's
have some attraction to the bond part
yes leave us credit card with that just
Juliet skillet this beautiful white
piece of this number nine Carlton yep
Nicola opinion but numbered super
douchey so in India in ancient
engineering now it was traditional to
burn the body and so if you're
particularly a trustee right both the
complexion and general shape of this
what am i eth america china fast forward
to the cremation related and so trusted
item recognized l got her skin this nice
shape dive tuck at the buddha during
didn't change when they cremated I was
on a flight I wasn't Daniel Daniel
yeah yeah but that's cough so out of the
store
I'm Jessie okay we're all gonna be
burning yeah okay
are you depressed depressed even aa good
shot so those are meditations you can
try that's it
especially with attraction to someone
else's part unless he's got a blemish
even your old partner if you're attached
to it which the Deaf and my definition
of lower school is my scholarship that
always works you might as well just
plant the seeds for a living diamond
body and not have to do this what is the
process the presided seminar tomorrow
the doll myself sick da Willoughby Smith
Nene of this Paquet epidemic but by the
way and this is something that people
don't talk about it teacher trainings at
the toy show me lieutenant
Virginia of a bikini ot3 ACI it's your
job to fashionable or Tom stone is lower
schools also why Pacino for the same
reason that reaching for specimens good
day settle snatches respond to get them
vitamin I have a friend named real
sister a study they gave she was sick
the game of vitamin D it made her more
thing nobly rebellion kidney different
vitamins
resonated I mean what is in the gang yet
so learn everything he's been adding to
his weight I have a tool by murders -
your mother's name learn all of them by
the message jijiksa if the Buddha taught
does not judge that look of what
emotionalism all right we're on the
second my nauseous primary negative
emotion and by the way you got your name
what's a there's six yes primary
negative meditations on the bottom
Dmitri Carson and if there's more yes
tiny assuming Doheny was cash disease
those 84,000 it's avoiding Buddhism they
stitch can't remember 84,000 that's cuz
in body for in 300g t-rex go very new
reason yes this is assisted this is the
most of a civil shite cigars the lean in
the Polka raspbian yes focus July and
compared with other crystals are quite
okay wait wasn't like 20 as I mentioned
yesterday 20 secondary negative buts its
study he's gonna teach them and then he
didn't because I saw a Neverland yeah
what I see - almost endless not enough
time to prepare if you're free that's
the one I'll teach you my suggestion
Stanley my young think about it for a
couple hours my special have I had that
one building when you void miss Michelle
maybe she'll pink can give you some from
her okay but I mean don't just read the
list across the budget is peace
experienced by your mom purchase okay
got it cuz we don't really know if other
people are having that experience Watson
the lady death so we may not get through
all six because after no okay
alright here we go that's number two the
bit more device but she got control knee
which means anger Guinea answer okay
here's the definition some chanting and
Jim my Impala you can have it
towards mr. human dictionary on Marshall
of a Spanish yeah you can have it
towards people but you can all do it
together
2003 Scott says oh boy yeah okay you can
have anger about anything the civil
watching option guy like anger speaking
of that happened to me okay awesome
Kunie nice them means angry mine the
lawyer says nine years Jerry okay I'm
from mine Sam do you know it's the
opposite of jumbo jam yang it means
rough it means like sandpaper grew back
that's Dutch a rough like nice to
touch anybody yet no Robert what's gas
last nickname in the monastery
every monk has a bad name oh there's the
world my mouth of monastery before where
prohibition young sisters gotta spell
you three Bart because I have a rough
complexion oh hey tree bark kinky Papa
okay don't call me senior father
cheeky Papa means man mr. tree bark it
means if you touch my skin the most
famous nickname is option a how they're
debating yes leave a bad impression
cuz we're paying for the Getty course
candidates food and yet lose an elephant
that time we didn't have any money
everybody was option was born it's a
yearly ocean generated try to name one
more she's like and so they were
supposed to debate yeah she show us the
bat Aviles with an anchor Katie class me
but I must tell me this
let's see there's a place in the debate
where you say yes when you quote our
book clevis is 0 it's a beautiful
bathroom but go buddy to the taxi
chasuble check the sutra says so track
of 1868 you share some mason verger so
the guy he was thinking about dinner
does in the chat that item there Momo
then guess what his nickname was for the
night okay anyway the word here is the
novice 7 my little bomb tree by angry
it's not nice to judge the opposite in
Sanskrit propeller and slow Sanskrit
season don't you yeah and the one who
speaks gently okay
it means sulk his mind manjushri is mind
is Manju Manju sure to blend George saw
shoulder cool alright your denim not
enough nepeta dip it after you get
number 2's you wanna hurt somebody
West Berlin America vs. cheetah kimochi
needs variate
mayor sovan is the passive name is the
special kind of aggression at the
Sorbonne a tip aggressive so like I
don't know you ask somebody for a
donation - Tata young editor that's ok
everybody no I'll pay yes you know I
won't eat for a week it's ok Yvonne
listen you you have the right to say no
but then we'll just cuz it yes I'll
probably have to stand bed
most of gravity dress losing weight
Oxenberg schemata that was possible to
karate I was angry like him yeah it's
possible at the progression
it's my yeah so Vinicius reassortant
okay it's menorca's possible is a
proscenium theater
alright jawsaw udemy Owatonna Sam Shin
do to be number change again how do you
get that calculate tree bark mine
you meet a trigger and we're gonna study
six triggers yes those APIs can say what
sets you off those that know it's a
prescribed well gets you angry
okay stop Kim I'll be subway missed I'm
gonna study them okay it's part of your
immediate with them as a chance Russia
eat enough at the ocean six ways to make
your means this person chance in front
of your face Olivia stable supposed
answer to it bidded Russian little not
around them everything's okay
yes you see them what who hurt me but
you mean Isaac okay children and to
teach you that the first trigger for a
negative emotion out of it they can you
get same name with the presence this the
woman you attracted to that's already
married
you see I mean Ellie priestess
translational Kotori bomber I would say
what's the antidote the Quincy dot yeah
avoid it's because we avoid them is it
ultimate antidote absolutely I know but
is it an antidote and the theater yeah
you should say immediately must be lower
school Ganesha Cola you know try to
avoid its biggest attention okay try to
avoid all people who piss you off but
this is one lower school method at the
Cox but let's assume you guys hsp90
centric circles never leave them
yesterday you know the women come here
to deliver Mount Sutro they bump into a
mark if you have karma yes Navasky is
Carter gonna meet them demostrated too
if a woman has changed once in a hundred
years
storage is definitely lower school
absolutely you say I'm never gonna talk
to you I'm on a plane but the change it
happened to Lydia ko it was interesting
it was okay some of that course to
chalice I spent a whole day marrying
this couple yeah and you had no part
they did they if they had this big big
plans and stay for like six hours but I
must never let in chess you know I
managed to suffer but domineers Lily's
is good then I'm sitting in a plane
yes you attend next to me is Rachel
McAdams some annoying unapplied and
I'm Lourdes didn't you co-pilot you know
I just married you I have a new policy
of charging people $10,000 that they get
divorced before years over ya don't want
oh yeah but this is a lot of brides I
guess the extreme but I managed to the
approach but what who your negative
question you got Stephen Watson I've
tried to avoid the trigger status big
guys down but there's no mystery
okay so anyway here it says Snover what
Wester says 9y tonight's budget sir
bless you mr. day on Vinny says well
what's the result but I'm glad he lived
a vanya which is wet sir yeah I was
gonna call it how to avoid anger or
never get upset level 10 is called
impossible angry yeah Damone that's why
it's not
and that means motioning your husband
yells at you might suppose that matters
when you have a son you can't get angry
near mother to that ultimate it so much
solute neither Sonia understand that the
person that we need my door open you
might there's a good way this was Mexico
car washes comfort people who life is a
mirror because I - isn't it easy come on
then suddenly they're real quiet
don't pretend she rejected a promoter
Santa with Regina
it sounds le coverage don't worry sister
yeah Harishchandra neurologist
chattering boy it was a visit how
irritating you are but I'm wants to take
him over some brass castle in a squall
Covey is coming but I must was it was it
bad pretend you walk into a room with
four pieces comatose chitter Meli's meet
I changed it was it higher middle okay
he's teaching a very large group mixed
there are high gases there they're high
on a boo child potato cheney enoguh
resna group yes yes Sarah Mary he's
having to mix in lower school no neobux
are you change counter D Kappa not get
that job now when we taught these data
we went into great detail ability to be
never yes cheetah hazard regards you
maniability bank account of good sees
more than negative emotions anger has
this you burn up when you kindness you
can Yahweh still hostin anything come
what is rich but he Hiroshi Sabrina yeah
I know
let's say it freezes them so you know
when you do the for PJ always agitated
sila part of the goal is to put the
seeds into suspended animation
what are you calling in and Cyril Jenny
yeah you want to freeze them
motion is a mirage ability seminar
Yeah right never open with the negative
awesomest thing with the positive see
this is very similar you can think of it
that way
well I still have them but they never
open but majesty if you scroll say at
the butcher all right
and by the way the question you asked
authorities are huge in the autumn the
channels matimak how's that it burns
your good seeds and you know are there
special conditions yes pretend no
slaughter huge domestic Romanesco set of
atomic objects in Quebec are you talking
about buddy suppose you said three in
that hot day Illya you know yes it is a
cheese stick around
so I started probably come in the
gardener was little bit you I got you
so he says kimchi kimchi means de Nieva
is that it destroys your good Dom stop
on the reservoir O'Shea Samina yeah you
could take them out of the refrigerator
majesty minutes it's why I didn't leak
I'm good with that but but there's books
written about this subject
no you have to continue madness in them
don't you play it alright you have an
atom
Vasek you skin should be a forest fire
stuff like that thousand bits genome but
my last category it yeah number 21 I
think I'm sorry for ya number four right
okay so when you meditate in the
afternoons did know that very it's
negative so just follow the process
levitating cartoon come this afternoon
if you have free time after your next
yes yeah firstly Russia but you know is
now Raymond for Tommy deteriorates in
Nevada tag when listen when your husband
yells are you okay bravas much it
nervous
my philosophy you know no I'm not gonna
yeah yeah
personally I don't see menagerie guys
tomorrow
you seen I mean like you're not worth it
- no it's point you okay - and there's a
joke in Buddhism especially don't go
online and fight was a sin just how
Rasta and good life dispersion that's
the best way to irritate yeah we got a
little bit more to go and then we're
gonna take a break I taught you this
morning that's a good way to keep your
students in the class I'm shameless copy
even if you don't intend to stop so is
it chat but um as far as an offset but
I'd avoid numerous Casal store is
thought of a go barista with negative
some Jade egg so yeah
kill each other each other it takes a
lot of patience then I go on TV and I
you know I thought this is it anger is
Joe's choice work to build guys to build
to raise children to have children and
raise them and it's just a thought it's
just I killed Cheney every person that
works so hard on them like a tree you
know we're so hard doc sitios not give
birth to this child
Palmateer Kristijan then you just send
them off to fight in some stupid with
the vinyl I get a talk at a military
academy in America yeah they're all
somewhat of a slit which tiny both sexes
to let's and boy
they they don't believe this Top Gun
stuff you know it's not romantic anymore
I think don't believe all these feelings
this is a famous Rambo movies it's not
borrowing that stuff America try to find
something blah he wishes America's a
variety mr. O'Shay McDonald don't take
all this poison stuff okay silent movies
not romantic
Top Gun is not romantic then you don't
mind seats now people lose their legs
they come today normalizes the wave is
not messed up reason you know something
okay not why not at the moment is now
shooting people in movies let's fill my
heart in your blood it all comes from at
the surf brace whoredom two seconds of
the mind movie is loosely fight books
0.9 you it's good order here why get all
mad at me but it is but you don't
stories like that when you newbie writes
it today again okay anyway if you can't
control your much the Cathar leader with
swear genious it will destroy countries
Ronny
okay this is chilly day thanks on I'm
almost done okay yeah I can see that I
can see it I'll do two more lines at the
asteroids give so one is for number one
and the one is for number two bit of a
blood neva
Lapierre over phone okay
thank our chicken Nikki llama took tomb
Sara double control iminium botany Kenda
meets Ian then there was a custom in the
secondary language for example we will
see the crisp attendances week sometimes
you can call it twilight language but
it's a language to refer to was it
selects and like eat so here ya soon as
possible my holy llamas it's hard
sometimes heats up more your decision to
edit or remove all that my suit I said
negative ayats and this device this is
my church dilemma she hits us yet that I
have it okay holy hard heat sometimes he
says listen he was a very honest man he
said things go very low a circuit or
irregularjinny ago he would look those
high Lamas in the we're talking
reincarnated Lama you know was look him
in the eye I didn't cut a nearest you
don't get pissed off of your students
I'm not gonna say holy hard is ha
yawns material at least the slaves
example diplopia laughs a lot of trouble
listen a student film okay go ahead a
new TV show family problem you can give
it a polite name but then he quotes a
famous book okay what is it and then
we'll tell you people just leave any man
no Stan speech once this toilet on
parity sedan taboo dick permit dick
permit supper supper taboo taboo got to
cut me okay so we gotta go to the car to
cut which in Sanskrit is tapas tapas
came into the word tepid it means he
spiritual he it doesn't share the horny
and it means tough price applause the
Nagas really practica genuine rambo
practical is sort of a throwback there's
a llama in serra one of my Islamic about
ready to Austin I will post he just the
Train tried to move and he tried to move
and he moved and the Train didn't
there's planes bigger say oh my God he's
our first he says got on that one sir
are you are these guys I don't know
stand out in the Sun all day you know
meditate in the snow okay but right now
verse knew if suppose the whole universe
Wow Wow with that llama mister Yeshua
and Shanti Davis says he should go out
at it so that that's not a lot
that's not a tough guy then yes sir
who stopped the train then you're slow
as compared to staying cool Sam doesn't
know much more genius and staying cool
in the kitchen when your husband goes
crazy kitchen - who taken an accordion
Kotori pretty much lost at sea educated
people deserve but that's the people who
takes courage to spend in the kitchen
no just angry that's cursed it's very
beautiful
don't you want a spiritual war it's like
the Honam it's one who doesn't yell h-
stop the war the people who maybe start
more brain check than the people who
fight worth Louise you got to rest
another night and you want brave
than the people who stopped worth on the
ground okay chef Dustin I'll do it when
it says nine not only emotionally text
or a snap don't worry isn't it just
because why first line share that table
with dick by mail if you rate bad karma
yes live we you know it's a blue car
most ownin I didn't yes of all the bad
comments our karma at the guinea
official number one it's an Abba dig by
me means there is no debt
Nick acquiesced number
if samurai second line says patience is
number one on the war here on this
number 18 now get off much more
difficult than shooting people with an
Augustine you just realize they put
aside the bomb but Anita course large
man stand there and push to keep cool in
the kitchen no mostly tobacco just a
near miss at but that one so if you can
do it you should feel proud of it you
know yes you can
okay let's talk people yelling good
coach at novice investor it's for you
stay near Buddha rostra Hiroshi
simulator Yanni Buddha belly chance
Panetta
alright take a break still imperative
with your boy in the mail
we only have half an hour and receive me
my think about a plug-in EF where
support we have another job this week
when I see shortly we are reviewing the
past eight years is doing it with
pictures easier service history those
who would like to be in a status
meditation or no variability of each eye
to the minimal immediate at soon if your
master degree yes or meditation dream
that said I'm supposed to be
doing them faster yeah those are the
dreamers yes
so this is the leftover from Thailand or
something okay that one disgust Ellis
sorry Jasmine
the entire okay Tim I'm on 78 which is a
young lady working on a computer and
yeah okay those and what we're doing is
review we're reviewing the whole big
long room in pictures for this
assignment let clearly we show you the
picture so I show you the pictures tell
me what the picture seconds starting
tomorrow the ability a picture that you
tried to memorize the picture that is
here toasters not you ready over Tim
okay I'll stall some more and yeah the
pictures are square thank you and they
also have colours on their own it Kim's
gonna print them out in my speech at a
matter bits after
by the way venerable Jigme had some fun
maybe you wanna do she was trying to
find the palace nice enormous
translation connect to the picture it
was it the torii at myself I'm working
with the Tibetan yeah Tibetan but if you
want to have fun yes but I need somebody
monk okay here we go
in the beginning of the lamb rim when a
channel 4 he starts for your first job
what courses okay before you start to
edit an item how cool so its traditional
in Buddhist I did sit with this mom to
sell the teaching before you give it
it's exactly like selling comes in grab
it cause it's what they did you say what
go buddy Tim do you realize how great
this stereo is you might ask why no
stereo like this on any and these tires
they're wrong black and okay okay so by
the way if we just started some room
which moment knock I think is say mr.
Wesson I started this and say yeah and I
shall at that course I talk about a
wonderful army that's cancer
why would I do that Tomoya Alex Dell
yeah because it's the meditation but
that strategy well yeah boy some little
Azad I started from the end of the left
don't stir yeah
to meditation okay and we studied the
end yes in the chat wanted to use we had
to talk about emptiness and then we
wanted to use meditation so what are we
gonna do is Dylan cook them when they
don't contact me again
we're gonna jump to another book my
pitiful box I wa I will not cover so we
already finished all the emptiness which
is not very long dojo check this Dale
its own couple here we go in m7 yeah
nice but you should work Muslim edema
attacks years no girls you dreaming
that's all don't get those near separate
civil Isis and I'll tell you something
cute about this picture that you're
gonna repeat back yeah I'm scheduled
question glass stove it's a TV it is
who's learning in this picture door is a
child which I know but the Katinka good
yes okay why daughter the children tease
the father said that's
intranet oh because he's from the paper
if we're here Oh max very difficult for
since law you know people say like dr.
Ruth wife we had dinner I'll just reach
out you Richard you don't know it
she took my phone and there's a llama
chief one she put weekend
I truly ate it in yes I'm good okay so
we resisted you know my generation
cousin tomorrow I'm good at to be
comfortable and you have Scott you know
yes Prussia custom nor could match the
betrayal HTML that's really why cause
the company says you messed up okay he
has I tend to be afraid I'm kind of a I
also think if I wait three years don't
have that attitude about this mom room
don't think don't make him over some pro
don't my sister know what yeah II guess
I can I have a job yes Anya I can't
learn just trainees you know share
everything you want you resisted that
way at the guys picture means
do be like the father would the chestnut
wasn't humble father
what's a new one a Liam those thumbs
innovation yeah Instagram I'm like it
sounds like a kind of confidence your
Instagram yeah Dylan stuck it up so when
you die good okay so there's two choices
you have
and get someone to help you gotta be
humble you can do it you can approach
emotionally affected to go very hard a
TOEFL easier to chest but don't matter
stand Rasta alright so if you see this
picture
yes stone is Kasia - don't be afraid of
this new tech column room yeah boy no no
but technology Columbarium he's a
cheetah no volition most people stop
learning after high school but just what
is it is that you
I need supervisor beach cottage yelets
you keep learning their whole life like
the car - I don't know next picture
leather jacket simcha there's a list of
reasons why you shouldn't come to a
teaching there's a lift
yes Pisa and alarm rim lumidee men of
lower motivation is committed by 2c okay
hi so I made up number one is blessing
to come to a teaching you want a blue
diamond mainly it's not wrong it's only
wrong if that's the only thing you want
yeah and I won't but it's a blessing
no it looks like a formative okay but
it's stupid God for blessing to some
people in Tibet
I cannot learn that the animal with the
pond yes don't come that's why you came
second strategy this a code word word to
put in your data bank to to get more
money later
say Yong Guk cut it - Jung Yong Guk it's
a special Tibetan word because your
friends are going friends yeah
why my friends going this yet you know
people just go because oh you know my
friends are going
that's what it means when you see this
picture you're gonna say oh I'm talking
about far away yeah yeah it almost
reminds me 3hm I just want to go to get
more information that I can teach in my
own class
ya basta you're not going to the
business question sir Maxim was somewhat
trying to improve myself by watching
[Music]
TJ yeah I sure was nice of course I was
to put it back at the performance of I
never take back without applying it to
you you chaste niche or otherwise you're
wasting your time
yes
now power in power means sulla
I will get more high position that's a
blessed if I know blessings you know she
told me to bushes lies - yeah which is
not that yabba-doo chisel - to join
Daniel Chinook on the last one is more
less interesting
okay you're like you want more
information - yeah cool that's the right
motivation
okay and if I treat myself I'll be able
to treat other people it's okay is
literacy bad but I'm a smuggle it should
read it today
all right Samantha next one snare the
show next one yeah okay
so if you met Einstein on a plane and
you didn't recognize he's on the plane
you're on a plane explain quantum
physics of every sneeze before he can
say no you started I see what that is
I have this happen to me so I'm not the
questions chalice yes I'll start
explaining Monica to me make obese now
it's all wrong
it happens in China sometimes people
start explaining diamond cutters I just
provide a business the other Stevie
Olivia the Queen you don't say I spent
25 years on that the point is myself Tom
stuff as I said yesterday comes from a
person who knows in English we have this
idiom mr. know-it-all yes that yes but
the Buddha really is no thank you
he sees everything one's night you know
all time thinking that of a donation to
him looking at your nose and looking at
your inner thoughts is the same it's
Madrid not vastness is saved in the
Russian Muslims ojou-sama he wrote on
the pucelle the sutras Sutra for you
personally
they love us ok don't he jump doubt it
nice invited him he wrote on the Pucelle
he gave this teaching to 2019 April
don't ask don't think he doesn't have
this capacity if you don't have that
capacity your weight because you're
trying to do it but I wish that the
reason was that yes
Shinobu Kotori so you can write booed
people who come to that we smuggling the
percentage change that you're talking
about a dr. mengele it is a dog who sees
the future of your disgusting visit
Buddha share Russian Subramani like they
say you need radiation treatment because
I'm good and you say why that's it it's
gonna fix you inside my atresia services
later when the diffusion change it's
what you need I thought why waste your
time with Jim personally I mean it
seemed in the Kikuchi show it's possible
yes it was your future already
communicating with you I used to see and
I would talk to you Michael future
Buddha Buddha I'm having a bad day yeah
people say what do you talk about when
you're in the toilet ok so if you can
get a TV from somebody like that yes
living it's much as you don't have to
add stuff Thank You chain yeah
don't drive me crazy when people say oh
this Buddhism it just needs a little
more psychology yeah you know the books
gonna disappear in two years
look it's what's in this jug or that you
know I'm like okay maybe nation being
might know what the Manchester's just
thought you know I don't maybe they
don't need ecology
Marsha at pet peeve I'm gonna teach you
this idiom whether you want to or not
yeah stealing it it drives me crazy you
can say it that way I allow you to say
it done Mexico that's drives me crazy
Buddhism that she needs Buddhism in the
car diluted the biotic boosie's was
written last year total bull and the
peace in the booth lasted for two and a
half years out in the pile copy you're
bullshitting you Creed's probably okay
you probably know it wouldn't have
survived never usually but Annabella
policeman a minute okay so I said it's
foolish to try to out thinking on
missions being something that was not
written by an omniscient being cheese
with someone's the Bible study next year
okay why waste your time hm you know I
know you 30 or 40 or you're 14
I don't know but uh I can tell you you
don't have time to read all the crap
that's a very young sketch don't you
know someone sent me this video send me
I don't have time I have this many years
I know for this year's psychology young
[Music]
jump into it I don't care I know the
name you said we can't watch movies yes
yes cuz I'll at the Buddhistic
responsibility to learn how to relax no
responsibility - it's a cut okay and we
did right fun day we were better
students so I didn't say you can't I
advise you well but don't spend the day
watching you yeah Triton anthem is dim
you must take your rest I bet it's a
better Buddhist you're better besides if
you take rest her mother
oh my gosh does a rough two days it
started with washing every dish in her
house I which was in this thing
after two days of serving and you learn
how to greet drinks at that dinner they
come out with a big tray of dessert you
know which one do you want I think why
do you think I want one
well once I said well now it's twice
learn how to okay if you can work and
work if you can't work yeah yeah but oh
it's a question I'm just saying don't
yeah just go ahead we need alright we
finished with anyone tomorrow what's
this better way do you have any
announcements oh let's do a Telemundo
Luca you in the mood
oh it's like sushi but it's sucky
okay okay
shinmin li laughing seen dead body
sungazing to make a drunken i'm - a lot
to show
come on leave him you should talk talk
she tsunami she'll let you know by
Connie
[Music]
we're gonna cover more of these tomorrow
and you'll get probably tomorrow you'll
get maybe sure I'm sure there's a quite
chimps case was after a boat this is the
review of the last okay but if you if
you wanna master's degree in dust that's
my student